Contact

michaelspencer90@hotmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/michaelspencer-bsn-rn-cmsrnbc-48558344 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals
Nursing
Nursing Management

Certifications
CMSRN

Michael Spencer BSN, RN, CMSRN-BC

Clinical Educator Specialist at HCA Healthcare Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Referencing HCA's mission statement, Above all else, I am committed to the care and improvement of human life. Throughout my career, I continue to strive to make a difference by leading change and influencing others. I analyze the impact of the patient experience and reflect how it helps grow the healthcare industry on a daily basis. Sometimes it just takes a smile to make all the difference in someone's life.

Experience

HCA Healthcare 5 years 10 months

Clinical Educator Specialist January 2020 - Present (6 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Staff Nurse

March 2019 - December 2019 (10 months)

HCA Houston Healthcare Clear Lake

4th floor Med/Surg Overflow

Nurse Manager

September 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 7 months)

Clear Lake Regional Medical Center

6th floor Heart Tower - Cardiac Telemetry/Med-Surg

Staff Registered Nurse

September 2014 - September 2017 (3 years 1 month)

Clear Lake Regional Medical Center

6th floor Heart Tower - Cardiac Telemetry/Med-Surg

Senior Care Centers Charge Nurse April 2014 - October 2014 (7 months)

Clear Brook Crossing

Skilled Nursing Facility

Education

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2013)